<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICan</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Info</string>
    <string name="ican_title_main">I CANanda</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hymn">Hymn</string>
    <string name="ican_hymn_main">I CANanda</string>
    <string name="title_canada_hymn">O Canada</string>
    <string name="subtitle_canada_hymn">(English version)</string>

    <string name="lyric_canada_hymn">O Canada! Our home and native land!
True patriot love in all thy sons command. With glowing hearts we see thee rise,
The True North strong and free! From far and wide, O Canada, we stand on guard for thee.
God keep our land glorious and free! O Canada, we stand on guard for thee.
O Canada, we stand on guard for thee. </string>

    <string name="title_activity_images">ICan Images</string>

    <string name="text0">Provinces</string>
    <string name="title_activity_alberta">Alberta</string>
    <string name="title_activity_british_columbia">British Columbia</string>
    <string name="title_activity_manitoba">Manitoba</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ontario">Ontario</string>
    <string name="title_activity_quebec">Quebec</string>
    <string name="title_activity_provinces">Provinces</string>
    <string name="title_activity_saskatchewan">Saskatchewan</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_brunswick">New Brunswick</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nova_scotia">Nova Scotia</string>
    <string name="title_activity_prince_edward_island">Prince Edward Island</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newfoundlandand_labrador">Newfoundland and Labrador</string>

    <!-- Alberta -->
    <string name="text_alberta_textA1">Alberta is a western province of Canada. With a population of
        3645257 in 2011 and an estimated population of 4145992 as of October 1 2014, it is
        Canada is fourth-most populous province and most populous of Canada is three prairie
        provinces. It is bounded by the provinces of British Columbia to the west and Saskatchewan
        to the east, the Northwest Territories to the north, and the US state of Montana to the
        south. Alberta is one of three Canadian provinces and territories to border only a single
        US state and is also one of only two provinces that are landlocked</string>

    <!-- British Columbia -->
    <string name="text_british_columbia">British Columbia, also commonly referred to by its initials
        BC, is a province located on the west coast of Canada.
        British Columbia is also a component of the Pacific Northwest and the Cascadia bioregion,
        along with the US states of Oregon and Washington. The province is name was chosen in 1858
        by members of the Hudson is Bay Company. In 1871, it became the sixth
        province of Canada. Its Latin motto is Splendor sine occasu Splendour without Diminishment.
        The capital of British Columbia is Victoria, the fifteenth largest metropolitan region in
        Canada, named for the Queen who created the Colony of British Columbia.</string>

    <!-- Manitoba -->
    <string name="text_manitoba">Manitoba is a province located at the longitudinal centre of Canada.
        It is one of the three prairie provinces and is the fifth-most populous province in Canada,
        with a population of 1.208.268 as of 2011. Manitoba covers an area of 649.950 square
        kilometres and has a widely varied landscape the southern and western
        regions are predominantly prairie grassland, the eastern and northern regions are dominated
        by the Canadian Shield, and the far northern regions along the Hudson Bay coast are arctic tundra.
        The province is bounded by Saskatchewan to the west, Ontario to the east, Nunavut and Hudson
        Bay to the north, and the US states of North Dakota and Minnesota to the south.</string>

    <!-- Ontario -->
    <string name="text_ontario">Ontario is one of the ten provinces of Canada,
        located in east central Canada. It is Canada is most populous province by a large margin,
        accounting for nearly 40 percent of all Canadians, and is the second largest province in
        total area. Ontario is fourth largest in total area when the territories of the Northwest
        Territories and Nunavut are included. It is home to the nation is capital city, Ottawa,
        and the nation is most populous city, Toronto. Ontario is bordered by the province of Manitoba
        to the west, Hudson Bay and James Bay to the north, and Quebec to the east, and to the south
        by the US states of  Minnesota, Michigan, Ohio, Pennsylvania and New York.</string>

    <!-- Quebec -->
    <string name="text_quebec">Quebec is a province in east-central Canada. It is the only Canadian
        province that has a predominantly French speaking population, and the only one to have French
        as its sole provincial official language. Quebec is Canada is largest province by area and
        its second-largest administrative division; only the territory of Nunavut is larger. It is
        bordered to the west by the province of Ontario, James Bay, and Hudson Bay, to the north by
        Hudson Strait and Ungava Bay; to the east by the Gulf of Saint Lawrence and the province of
        Newfoundland and Labrador; it is bordered on the south by the province of New Brunswick and
        the U.S. states of Maine, New Hampshire, Vermont, and New York. It also shares maritime borders
        with Nunavut, Prince Edward Island, and Nova Scotia. </string>

    <!-- Saskatchewan -->
    <string name="text_saskatchewan">Saskatchewan is a prairie province in Canada, which has a total
        area of 651.900 square kilometres and a land area of 592.534 square kilometres,
        the remainder being water area. Saskatchewan is bordered on the west by Alberta, on the north
        by the Northwest Territories, on the east by Manitoba, and on the south by the American
        states of Montana and North Dakota. As of December 2013, the population of Saskatchewan was
        estimated at 1.114.170. Residents primarily live in the southern half of the province.
        Of the total population, 257.300 live in the province is largest city, Saskatoon, while 210.000
        live in the provincial capital, Regina. Other major cities include Prince Albert, Moose Jaw,
        Yorkton, Wynyard, Swift Current, and North Battleford.</string>

    <!-- New Brunswick -->
    <string name="text_new_brunswick"> </string>

    <!-- _Nova Scotia -->
    <string name="text_nova_scotia">Nova Scotia is one of Canada is three Maritime provinces and
        constitutes one of the four Atlantic Canada provinces. Its provincial capital is Halifax.
        Nova Scotia is the second-smallest province in Canada, with an area of 55.284 square
        kilometres, including Cape Breton and another 3.800 coastal islands. As of 2011,
        the population was 921.727, making Nova Scotia the second most densely populated province in
        Canada. </string>

    <!-- Prince Edward Island  -->
    <string name="text_prince_edward_island">Prince Edward Island is a province of Canada consisting
        of the island of the same name, as well as several much smaller islands. It is one of the
        three Maritime Provinces and is the smallest province in both land area and population.
        It is the only province of Canada to have no land boundary. The island has several informal
        names Garden of the Gulf referring to the pastoral scenery and lush agricultural lands
        throughout the province; and "Birthplace of Confederation or Cradle of Confederation,
        referring to the Charlottetown Conference in 1864, although PEI did not join Confederation
        until 1873, when it became the seventh Canadian province. The backbone of the economy is
        farming, as it produces 25% of Canada is potatoes. Historically, PEI is one of Canada is older
        settlements and demographically still reflects older immigration to the country, with Celtic,
        Anglo Saxon and French last names being overwhelmingly dominant to this day.</string>

    <!-- Newfoundlandand Labrador -->
    <string name="text_newfoundlandand_labrador"> </string>


</resources>
